I don't want to be in high school anymore.
Can I go back to middle school, please?
How many times are you going to say that, dude?
I yearn for my motherland.
You can just say your hometown.
But you've got lots of pals at your new school.
Don't get me wrong, I'm not complaining about my friends.
It's more like I don't vibe with the school itself.
This news fest?
Yeah, it's always got this creepy, empty silence.
We could really use more dumbasses.
Not sure if I dig the implication there.
I don't mean idiots, I mean dumbasses.
Remember third year when we'd all have fun and be dumb after class?
Me, Yamada, and Niyu.
That's an all-star study group right there.
The good old stupid days.
Study group is kind of a stretch.
If anything, goofing off all the time was killing our brain cells.
Yeah, murder them all!
He's starting to freak me out.
None of us were in any club,
so we could just devote all of our would-be practice time to goof-maxing.
We lifted up back then.
We were cringe, but we were free!
And thinking back now, it's...
It's heavy, man.
Straight up monologuing, okay?
And Yamada thought he was too good for our paradise after he got a girlfriend.
Whack as hell.
Hey, don't turn me into the bad guy here!
Sometimes when the sun sets, I'll walk down the roads I took to middle school just to feel something.
You good, dude?
I hear our old choir songs echoing, and the tears just won't stop.
Oh no, he's not good at all.
You have to treasure those precious moments while you've still got them,
because one day they'll slip through your fingers like sand.
So that's what Rihi said.
My man is going through it.
Sad.
Huh?
He's just hung up on the past.
It's not that deep.
Meany, bobeany.
Oh, my middle school was too fun.
My lobster was too buttery.
My steak was too juicy.
By the way, whose bride idea was it to go and invite Suzuki?
Are you cool with that?
Yeah, I don't decide who she gets to hang out with.
Even thinking about it too much would be disrespectful,
because then it's like I don't trust her.
But thanks for worrying about us.
What is this?
What did you get so confident?
Is that bad?
Ugh, I hate you, bro.
What?
I hate you, bro.
Sin, cosine, tangent
心の角度が広がって
電流が走る一目惚れ
覚えていてフレーニング
純度100%の想いも
一心伝心させたいな
君とあたしは正反対
恋はいつも想定外
ねえねえ聞いて
言葉を尽くして君に伝えたいの
心が体に追いついて
気づけば目で追ってる
眼鏡を外してさ
ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出したの
放課後まで待てない
大事な言葉ほど
酸素を嫌うみたい
辞書にないあたしなりの言葉で
早く早く早く早く
君に伝えなきゃね
どういうふうに伝えなきゃ
言っていなきゃ
猛が見つけた
そうやって
や魔のにとことを
早くは
まだ我々は
やまま
たぶんは
元々が
想念ながら
引っかりする
急ぎ
経擇
これで
遇われて
I won't ask any questions until he brings it up himself.
If it didn't go well, I would have no idea what to say.
And even if it did go well, I'd still have no idea what to say.
I'm such a jerk.
And now for a brief snowcap of Yamada's Festivod fun time.
Did you take this one?
Uh-huh.
Really? Sick.
Come on, just spit it out, Nishi.
I'm sorry I'm a terrible texter.
I'm sorry I'm so weird that I made it seem like I hate you.
I'm so awkward I can't even apologize for being awkward.
Hey, listen, I...
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
For texting you and all that.
If someone I didn't know asked me for my number, I'd be creeped out.
I get it. I was coming on way too strong.
I mean, who wants a stranger bothering them like that?
Point is, I gotta think harder before I act.
My bad.
Sorry, were you gonna say something?
Uh...
I, uh...
I'm sorry too.
I'm not used to texting people.
Up until now, I mostly just used my phone to talk to my parents.
I'll message home or someone every once in a while, but that's it.
I worry I'll write something weird, and I worry about typos or spend hours writing a stupid long text, and I worry about how long it is and how long it took to reply.
I would just talk on the phone, but I'm even worse at that than texting.
Still, despite all that stuff, I like texting you.
I know I overthink everything because I'm scared of making mistakes, but I'm gonna try my best to find a way to stop doing that.
We're total opposites.
Whenever you'd send something, I'd just text back right away without thinking.
I never thought you said anything weird.
Not even once.
Plus, I don't pick up on little details, so I probably wouldn't even notice if you goofed something up.
Oh, you should practice on me.
I'll be your dummy.
I'm chill.
You don't have to be scared of messing up with me.
I'm too dumb to notice.
And if I ever get annoying, you could just tell me, okay?
Say, shut your yap trap, idiot.
Easy.
I never say that.
Not that way.
Willst thou shish it?
What is that?
Am I a princess now?
Oh, Rihi, I forgot.
I gotta head out.
See her out, okay?
Is it cool if we talk at school, too?
Yes, of course!
Nice.
Later days.
After that sunny interaction, the frost between them melted away like the winter snow.
You've been in a weirdly good mood since the festival, Yamada.
And I see your eyes darting around, scanning the room for her.
But I'm not gonna bite.
I am made of stone!
Yamada, are you looking for someone?
Yeah, just Capacho.
Oh, now you're just touching me.
But I will not be provoked!
I don't know why I'm surprised.
Both Yamada and Tani are good guys.
Of course someone likes them.
Of course they can accept that like normal people.
This isn't gonna work, Taira.
Your personality's just different than I thought it'd be.
I gotta push those memories down.
I couldn't be more different from Yamada's dumb friend.
Acting like middle school was so great and high school isn't.
What is that guy even talking about?
You don't get to choose your elementary or middle school, so they're hell for a lot of people.
He could at least acknowledge that much.
But even if he did, I think I'd still be chill.
You weren't even saying anything?
Need my music time to decompress, okay?
Do you think this is funny too?
I'm not laughing.
Well, you should jerk.
Suspect doesn't typically jerk to the tube, which could only mean he's going into work.
Elementary.
Shall we take a little detour to the convenience store today, Tani?
What? No.
Sure, that's fine.
It's not though.
Well, quick.
Just make us some soft serve, please.
Our store doesn't have the machine for that.
And my shift doesn't start till later, so I won't be able to help you.
Aw, we could wait for him, Tani.
Or you could go home.
What's that noise for?
And he takes the bait.
What does it matter if I'm there or not?
It's just a store.
Huh?
Because it's fun having you around, dummy.
Come on, back me up.
It is.
Hmm.
Is that so?
Well, I guess it's fun.
I want a free ice cream now.
Gimme, gimme.
Will you please just leave?
It's Yamada.
What now?
Do I say hello?
Starting a conversation?
You should practice on me.
I'll be your dummy.
I'll do it.
Yo, Nishi.
Oh.
Uh, sorry.
That came out wrong.
I wanted to say hi to you first, but then you said yo, and it sort of caught me off guard.
Man, that's good.
You're hilarious, Nishi.
He thought I was funny.
Um, hey, Hon.
Look who's here.
Good morning.
Oh, hey, guys.
Did you just lose your dentures or what?
Seems like you're getting along really well.
I guess so.
I need details.
What do you think of Yamada so far?
Huh?
He makes my heart beat fast.
But it's like...
Like what?
I don't know.
It's a strange feeling.
I wonder what it could be.
It's a strange feeling!
I wonder what it could be!
What in the heart, I tell, is this?
The strange feeling.
Would you say it's like your heart aches for him or burns for him or...
Oh, no.
It's nothing fancy like that.
It's not fancy.
That helps.
I just don't know if it's Yamada or the situation.
Like, is my heart beating fast because of him or is it a panic attack?
Oh, okay.
We're getting real real today.
Every time I talk to a boy, my heart starts pounding like crazy and I don't have enough
experience to understand why.
I can't tell how much of it is Yamada and how much of it is just me.
Self-aware.
Respect.
Well, I'm relieved.
Don't think I could sit through another rom-com where the lead girl's totally dense.
What?
Forget I said anything.
Even if it is just the situation making your heart pound, why does that matter?
Because then it's like anyone would do.
Like I'm using him!
Hmm...
Is it, though?
I say it isn't worth thinking about.
Your heart's beating fast because you're anxious.
No question there.
You're just wondering if you'd still feel the same feelings even if it was someone other
than Yamada making you feel them, right?
I think so.
But does this hypothetical someone else even exist?
I guess not.
So you're pitting Yamada against Schrodinger's cat boy for no reason at all?
Those worries aren't real.
They're nothing.
You're just pulling new problems out of thin air.
You could do that forever.
Get hung up on reality all day, but these pointless what-ifs?
Let him go.
Maybe just start with how do I feel about him for now.
You're right.
And honestly, that's enough.
But still, I can't even get that far until I can talk without getting nervous.
There's no denying that.
Like I said, guys and girls both bleed the same color of red if you stab them.
Reminds me not to get on Hone's bad side.
Don't lose any sleep.
Just put in some practice and in a while you won't be so nervous anymore.
Then you'll know what's making your heart beat so fast.
Or who's making it beat fast.
And I'll be right here to back you up the whole time.
Hone, you don't get shy around people at all, do you?
I'm so jealous.
I don't think it's a matter of me being shy or not.
I have this sort of mild disdain for everyone regardless of their gender.
Oh, good for you.
Come on, guys.
Let's go.
It should have been a foul.
No.
Thanks for your help.
It was so busy today.
Yeah, of course.
You know, up until recently, Tawny and I hadn't talked much.
My heart would pound because I didn't know what he was thinking.
But we talked a little at the festival,
so being around him doesn't make me as nervous as it did before.
Way to kill the cops, Suzuki.
You sent it flying through the flipping window.
Out of bounds, girl.
I don't control the wind, you big jerks.
It's Tawny!
Oh, Anishi!
Yahoo!
What?
Hey, since when are you Anishi friends?
I've never seen you guys hang out.
Who cares?
We're friends now.
Lay down, Anishi.
Oh, I shouldn't have come along.
This was a mistake.
I didn't know you played badminton.
Oh, the old wacky wacky.
I haven't balled in a while.
Gotta practice or my minton will get bad.
There's no ball in badminton.
And your minton is very bad.
Wait, you should be practicing his running.
I've mastered the old wacky job.
You laughed.
I'm sorry.
It's just...
He said I'm minted his back.
How is that funny?
I'm so sweaty.
The wind feels extra chilly.
Gnarly.
Oh, crap.
Do I stink?
I went too hard.
Excuse me?
Since when do you care about personal hygiene?
Did you rehearse that?
So, Nishi, you laugh a lot, huh?
What?
I'm so embarrassed.
This is the nervous kind of heart pounding for sure.
Yeah, I want to fix that, but I can't tell that sometimes...
Fix it?
Why fix something good?
I don't think you need to change.
My heart...
I'm dying.
Yamada, if you're that worried about stinking, put on some of this.
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
So, uh...
What kind is this one?
Oh, it's cool, man.
Oh!
I can't!
What is this nap?
I'm freezing my napsob!
I know.
I hate it, so I figured I'd just give it to you.
What, am I a trash can to you?
It's easy to make me laugh, but I don't think that's it.
Yamada makes it easy for anyone to laugh when he's around.
Told ya!
What?
What is happening?
Hey, Tani.
Morning.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Yes!
I had a normal human interaction.
I'm so sleepy.
Whoa!
What the...
Oh, how's it going, Tani?
What did I just witness?
Tani, what were you and Nishi talking about just now?
Huh?
Nishi?
Where?
Nothing.
We told each other good morning.
Are you sure?
She flipped out and ran away over a good morning.
I guess.
Oh.
Hmm.
Quick question.
Hmm?
Can you tell me what Nishi's like?
What?
Well, you both work in the library, so you must know her pretty well.
One might say, intimately.
Uh, no, I wouldn't say that.
Hmm.
I see.
Aw.
He says the beef katsu rolls are all sold out.
That sucks.
Hey, Tida.
Could I ask for your advice?
Huh?
Advice from me?
Like, about what?
So, Suzuki suddenly developed an interest in the girl who works with you?
Yeah.
I can tell there's something specific bothering her, but I can't tell what.
I mean, it's pretty obvious, right?
She thinks you've got a side piece, duh.
A side piece?
Come on.
You're spending time with another girl.
Of course she's jealous.
You're sure?
I haven't done anything to make her feel that way.
To be honest, I can't imagine Suzuki being jealous at all.
She's too positive of a person.
Yay!
Fair enough.
Well, if Suzuki is jealous, then it's probably because she thinks you're not paying enough attention to her.
It's okay to be mad about it.
Come on, get mad.
Do you want us to fight?
I see what's happening.
You're into the idea that she's jealous.
Of course, it's all coming together now.
A part of you wants her to be jealous because it validates your worth as a boyfriend, even if it's not exactly in character for her.
But you're still not confident, so you need validation from me, too.
Is that it?
Sorry, it's not like that at all.
Or is it?
Wait.
Huh?
It's you guys.
When did you start hanging out?
Geez, overreact much?
Sorry, I guess.
What's up today?
Working in the library again?
Yep.
Meaning Neishi will be there, too.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I see.
Roger that.
Suzuki, is something bothering you?
Check it out!
Toy central, baby!
I love this stuff!
Yamada, remember D?
Whoa!
Oh, hell yeah!
I missed my chance to ask her.
I was able to say hi to Tani.
The second I saw Yamada, I folded out of there like a weirdo.
I thought I was finally getting better at talking to him, but now I'm getting worse.
I'm devolving!
I see what's happening.
You're into the idea that she's jealous.
Is that true?
No.
If I'm happy because she's worrying, then that means our relationship isn't equal.
Also...
Even if your mind is cloudy or you're still processing something, I want you to know that
if you ever feel anxious or on edge about anything, you can talk to me.
I want to be that way for her, too.
If there's something she wants to say, I want to hear it.
She shouldn't feel anxious about us.
I don't want to be the cause of that.
If she suspects me of something, that's my own fault.
This is turning into a replay of Summer Break.
At this rate, I'm going to end up with the exact same regrets.
Even if I'm scared, I can't run away next time.
There's no point in wondering what she's thinking or how she's feeling.
I won't find the answer on my own.
I'm just making up fears for myself.
It's getting pathetic.
The next time I see her...
The next time I see him...
I'll just ask.
I'll just talk to him.
What up, Nishi?
Oh, and Tani, too.
Team Lebe!
Oh, come on.
Say something.
I'm losing it already.
Now that the moment's here, I can't look him in the eye.
Suzu King?
Yo, Nishi!
Come and blow bubbles!
You missed out on the other stuff, but you're here just in time for Bubba-palooza.
Uh, Bubba-palooza?
You're a star, so you can take this one.
Yamada's got the bubble juice right over there.
Um...
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
I'll never forget this kindness!
Okay, Fancy!
Hi, buddy!
I've got you now.
So, Nishi, you laugh a lot, huh?
What?
Now that I think about it...
I got my glove out to catch feelings, you know?
Same school?
Different class?
Shy?
Fix it.
Why fix something good?
I don't think you need to change.
Look!
It's her!
It's totally her!
Yamada's got Nishi fever!
Then this morning...
No!
What the...
Oh, how's it going, Tani?
What did I just witness?
Her face with tomato machine bolted after seeing Yamada!
Whoa!
This is moving fast!
They've already made a left connection!
Good thing I kept Yamada here till the library closed!
Suzuki...
Why did you ask me about Nishi so many times today?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to learn more about her so she could be my new buddy.
And you do work with her!
Can you tell me what Nishi's like?
Zero subtext.
I should have known...
Hey, are you alright?
You're all purpley.
Are you gonna barf?
Kill me.
Why?
Sorry Suzuki dragged you into this.
She's a lot.
It's fine.
This is fine.
Guys, Yamada's flexing for some reason.
Come on, let's go pretend to be impressed.
Let's go pretend to be impressed.
97.5 voice.
Let's go Всابس.
Go alltså.
He 어.
ノ
cken enables.
Yeah.
You have to go.
Well, let's go.
At this time, I hope you make sure your58ук.
It would've been better.
I wish we had a child I come on.
It's so strange,
Do you think so fun?
I heard that it's clear
It's clear that
You can't tell it,
Dr payer
After that,
twenty six hour
It's mine
It's special
Thank you.